# Ramadhan Mohammed Mkoma

**Q** 255766570255

@ Ramadhanmkoma9@gmail.com

Zanzibar Central/South, Tanzania

Names: Ramadhan Mohammed Mkoma, 23 yrs old. A Computer science student at The State University of Zanzibar (SUZA) - Degree Holder.As a CS Student, i am mostly dealing with creating programs, web development, Android Apps Development through different kinds of new Technologies, also i like problem solving and volunteering. I look forward to further my knowledge and becoming an expert on Tech stuffs so as to help solve the society problems by providing better and intelligent solutions and ideas using the knowledge i have got.

### **EDUCATION**

# University of Dar es salaam Computing Centre (UCC)

Diploma in Computing and Information Technology

Ct, 2018 - Oct, 2020

3.5 GPA

# Ubungo islamic high school

O'level

**a** Jan, 2013 - Nov, 2016

Division 3 GPA

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### **Spice Techs**

**Ethical Hacker** 

# Wireless Security (Wireless Penetration Testing) includes

Information Gathering (Network Enumeration, Identifying SSID in Scope and Inrange)

Vulnerabilty Analysis (Foot-prints, MiTM)

Exploitation (Creation of Executive and Detail technical report)

🛗 Aug, 2022 - Oct, 2022 🙎 Mchina Mwanzo, Zanzibar

# The State University of Zanzibar (SUZA)

Web Developer & Networking

Networking

Configuring Switches and Routers Managing network Cables using Trunks Managing Switch ports Creating & Testing Ethernet Cables

# Web Development

Creating Front-end Website - HTML, CSS & JavaScript
Taking Free Code Camp Front-end Courses for certification



# **UDSM Computing Centre (UCC)**

IT Technician

IT Technician

Managing Operating System
Program installation & Repair
Troubleshooting Computer Hadware & Software

Computer Hardware Management

Aug, 2018 - Sep, 2022 Mlimani, Dar es Salaam

# **SKILLS & INTERESTS**

#### **Skills**

Soft Skills

**Technical Skills** 

#### **Interests**

Data Science; Website Design; Cybersecurity; Mobile App Development; Computer Science; Web Development; Al

# **LANGUAGES**

# **English**

Speaking (Very Good)

Writing (Very Good)

Swahili

Speaking (Very Good)

Writing (Very Good)

# **REFFERENCE**

#### Mr Massoud Hamad

Lecturer, The State University of Zanzibar

Phone: 773500429

Email: massoud.hamad@suza.ac.tz

# Mr. Abuubakar Mchowera

Customer Service, Piki Delivery Company

Phone: 738634923

 $\textbf{Email:} \verb| cozybwoy99@gmail.com|\\$ 

### Dr. Maryam Khamis

Lecturer, The State University of Zanzibar

Phone: 773455565

Email: maryam.khamis@suza.ac.tz